Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for your patience. The time has come.
I would like to start the final Ortivi special now.
This is the last Ortivi, so thank you so much for your applause and cheers!
Now, let's get to the members!
Oh, what should I do?
Are they already here? Oh, it's okay.
If you have the members appear, they will come from the back, from over there.
Yes, please.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen.
Good afternoon.
And so it begins.
Morty Bee's final special.
It's over.
Oh, well...
Mmm.
Ha-ha-ha
Ha-ha-ha-ha
I put in too many weird outlines.
Ha-ha-ha
It's good to hear your voices after all these years, everyone.
Thank you very much
Thank you very much.
Oh!
Oh.
Ooh.
Ooh!
Let me start by introducing myself as a member.
Yes. Nanohan Aoyama, I am a junior high school student.
I am 14 years old.
Good morning!
Yes, I'm Nekorna, 22 years old.
I am the mayor of Tyne High School. I am 21 years old.
Yes, I'm Aya Shirahama, third-year junior high school student, at 14 years old.
Yes, so once again, the final Voltibee special public recording!
Thank you all for coming.
Thank you very much.
Hello to all of you who came yesterday.
Kombun for those of you who are watching the broadcast.
Kombun
This time, we're going to show you a video recorded at Alice's Aqua Garden in Tamachi.
This time, we are presenting a video recorded at Alice's Aqua Garden in Tamachi, Tokyo.
As of now, it's 12:00 noon on Saturday, April 8.
So, as long as nothing special happens...
I think that the recording will be available just a few hours later.
That's amazing.
That's great.
But, you know, basically, the recording will be distributed as is,
I can't ask them to cut it out,
What?
That's right.
You were going to ask for various things?
Well, if we weren't here on the radio, we'd have the feel of a live broadcast.
It could work, couldn't it?
Don't say that.
Today, it feels like a live broadcast.
So, you know, when it came on the air, it was Bolt. It was a bolt.
That's amazing.
You have to say something.
Like, Hinachi-chan is in some kind of trouble.
So, it's been a week since the new school year started on Saturday, April 8,
Two ninth graders, huh?
A new school year is fun!
That's early.
I think I Instagrammed out what group I was going to be.
I wanted to be so badly.
I'm in the first group.
You're really obsessed with Ichikumi, aren't you?
No, I was writing a 3rd grade assignment at the end of my 2nd grade year.
I was asked to write until the end of the third year,
I guessed the number of the 3rd grade, and I got it all right.
I guessed all of them,
I got them all right,
I wanted to be a member of Ichikumi,
Don't you have a strong image of Ichikumi?
Yes.
Yes, they are. It can be strengthened.
The second year Ichikumi was very strong,
They wrote almost all of the graduation ceremony, chorus school, and ball game competitions,
I was in the third group of the second year,
I was in the third group of the second year, and we didn't win a single award,
That is why I want to do my best to win many awards in the 3rd year group.
What is it? Yumiyoshi Chu
I was in the first group that won three volumes last year.
Oh, no!
Are you going to do it?
I haven't done anything yet, but...
I took it.
I think it's strong.
I think it's a select group.
I think so.
Very pichon.
How are you doing, Nasu?
I'm in group 4.
Aren't you strong? Not strong enough?
From now on, please use hearts.
Heart.
I'm so happy to have my favorite teacher and my favorite friend for 3 years,
But my friend is in the Hydrogen department, so we have Asari and so on.
I have a lot of new classmates and kids I don't know,
I thought, "Oh no, what am I going to do, I'm going to be the only match,
That's so cute. What? I asked him what it was, and he told me all about it.
Thank you very much.
I'm glad you guys enjoyed yourselves, even though you just started.
I'll give you a quick update on what we've been up to.
Yes, we are.
I am thinking.
I, Ryuto, recently went to Ohanami (cherry blossom viewing).
Did any of you go to see cherry blossoms?
With Chicha?
Maybe with Axta?
I really wanted to show cherry petals on my head,
I know that petals don't go on the head if you aim for them.
I have an image of them on the shoulders of men who are not conscious of them.
It's a nice touch.
But I made a reel or something on social media,
I'm putting it up, so please take a look.
And your seniors?
I'm in the sauna. That's all.
Good night.
Isn't it hot already? Because it's already hot outside,
In winter, it's like taking a sauna to get warm,
It's just right now.
It's really just right now?
It's not cold, but the wind is cold,
It's really great.
There are people who are doing the same thing.
It's like a sauna seminar.
Like a sauna seminar.
Hey, don't look at me,
Don't look at me.
The party is this way,
No, it's not.
It's definitely a party.
It's a seminar.
I see.
Did you guys lose track of when you were supposed to be sitting down?
Sure did.
Sure, sure.
Please have a seat.
Excuse me.
A chair?
A chair.
Hello, I am the voice of heaven.Hi, I am the voice of heaven.
I don't know, the response to my self-introduction was just too much,
It took so much time.
I was so happy to see such a great response to my self-introduction.
I was so happy.
There will be a scoring session later today,
So let's go to the title call, shall we, Chi-chan?
I'd like to go. Are you okay?
Yes, I think so.
Let's go to the final stage of "Boltimie"!
I'm really happy to see such a big applause.
I'm so happy.
That's great.
Wash your hands.
So, this is Folbybee...
I've been doing a lot of things.
Yes, we have.
How much do you think I've done? How many times?
How many times? Uh...
Yeah, I've done...
But I'd say over 50.
I hope so.
Five dead.
One hundred.
Boom.
80 times or so.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
But, you know, even before they named it Boltivie.
That's totally different.
Who named him Boltivie?
I don't know... such a beautiful name.
I'm sure there was some kind of survey.
And they came out on top.
It was decided.
Oh, it's me.
Applause
Yes, it is. Takaishi Momo-san, it's you.
Yes, it is.
Yes, that's me.
So, I have done many things in my professional life,
I'm sure you have many memories,
I would like you to share your memories with us today,
I would like to talk about some of the memories I have with you today.
I have created this section for you today.
Let's go.
Let's go,
Many things have happened.
Morning TeeVee 00 Station
Now that you've looked back at all of the VOLTYBE delivery so far, I'm sure you'll agree that this one is the best,
I think I can't choose the best one,
I don't think I can choose anymore,
I can't pick one at all, but I'm torn.
I don't think I can pick one, and I can't pick one at all either, but I'm not sure,
Everyone wrote in their sketchbooks, right?
I have written it down.
So, who would like to go first?
Who would like to go first?
I'll go first.
Oh, sorry. Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Uh, my 00, uh, not the 00 ambassador.
My general, my general, my general,
My general, my general..,
Jang! Milky is yours, isn't it!
There may be quite a few of you who wonder what this is,
I want to eat milky now! is coming up.
This is what I wanted to do for the summer festival with everyone,
There was a time when I wanted to hold a summer festival with everyone, and we were able to make it happen on Decor TV,
We played games, and it was like a summer festival,
We had a summer festival atmosphere with yukata (summer kimono) and games,
There was a tea-like game.
There was a tea-like game,
Some senior,
One of the seniors?
Some senior wanted some milky,
A senior wanted a milky.
That's right.
I was able to hit about three times in one game,
I got to about the second one and couldn't hit it at all,
That's when the famous words came out,
I want to eat milky! That's when Rina-chan said, "I want to eat milky,
She said she wanted to eat milky.
Was she lying?
If she said that much,
Every time I did Voltiview,
I had been thinking about it all the time.
I wanted to eat milky.
That's right.
So, if you say that much,
The milky is yours.
Please watch Vol TV to see the result.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
The match, you know? All of you.
Yes, yes
Everyone was cute, wearing yukata
We all looked so cute in yukata!
Runa, did you enjoy the milky?
At that time...
It was delicious.
When the sweat and tears mixed together...
I'm scared.
Did I hit it off right?
I was just looking at the guys, and I was like...
I was just looking at them.
Bye, Aya!
What's your advice for Luna-chan?
Please give me some advice.
She said, "Please give me some advice for Luna-chan.
I couldn't help but give a little "kiai" to her.
It's the spirit of proximity.
We all put our energy into it.
And we were able to hit it!
I was able to hit it!
When I saw Milky at the supermarket
I see Luna-chan.
It's delicious!
I think I'll make Milky Haruna's flavor.
Milky is now
Milky has become my blood and flesh.
Scary.
Don't turn it into a TV horror show.
Scary, huh?
Well, if you haven't seen it.
I'm sure you'll enjoy it.
Okay, who's next?
Okay, here we go.
My Volt TV picks.
The winner of the "00 Award" is...
Vol TV.
It's the outfit that made me smile.
What kind of costume?
It's not a costume.
It's a costume.
It's a blooming flower.
I'm not supposed to explain it.
This is for the upcoming release of Bolt's Smile Flower song,
When the release of the song "Smile Flower" by Bolt was near, each member brought in a project to make everyone smile on Bolt TV,
Aya was doing a rakugo storytelling project, I think,
Aya-chan was doing rakugo, I think.
Aya-chan asked the members to perform Rakugo,
So Nano-chan sang a song with a smiley flower on it,
And Rumpin was doing something I don't understand,
I think only the fans who got into the music video of Smile Flower.
I can't put the music video into words, so please watch it.
And then I did a picture-story show, and that's where my original character, the legendary Ilfra, was born.I did a picture-story show, and this is where my original character, the legendary Ilfra, was born.
I chose this episode because I think there are probably some people who did not know about Bolt at that time,
I chose this episode because I think there are people who didn't know about Bolt at that time, and I would like them to watch this episode.
It was the reindeer of summer, wasn't it?
Summer reindeer?
Summer horror.
Oh, horror.
But Aya, you were talking rakugo, but it was like a colloquial story.
I've been thinking about it a lot too.
I should have read it perfectly, but I panicked a bit,
I dumped a lot on the members.
I was panicked, so I gave a lot of ideas to the members.
I had already written an essay in advance,
But when I looked at it, I saw that I had written a lot of things that I hadn't written.
It was all right.
I missed it.
And Chi-chan's Ilfra too.
That's right.
It became a thing, right?
Yes, it did.
We did a review of it,
And now it's loved by the world.
I'm going to leave you with today's Lionel Nano.
I'm going to go through the archives and look at everyone.
I'm kind of impressed.
I can't.
But that time, you know, I was really touched by the way you changed Nano-chan.
I see.
But I'm really glad it was the last one.
That's right.
Why? Because everyone is weird?
No, no, no, no.
It's too bad.
Nice try.
Almost.
It's too bad.
I'm not the one who says it like it's too close. I'm more of the deliver it type.
Last one's fine.
Oh, we delivered it, too.
Oh, I see.
Oh, yeah.
No, it's just the timing.
Oh, shoot.
Nice battle.
Three for three.
That's good.
You gave me a team.
Thank you.
I'm glad we got it right.
No, no, no, no, but it was a good turn.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes, I'd love to have you all do that.
Thank you very much.
Okay, I'll go.
Oh!
That's it!
I'd like to win a prize for winning the hearts and shoulders of our guests!
Oh!
I'm sure many of you know who I'm talking about,
This is the time when Yuzuki Okura and Mr. Setoguchi from Yuzuki's Room came to the show as our guests.
Until then, Chie and I had been visiting Yuzuki's room together,
I didn't really have a chance to talk with Ainoma-chan,
I have not really had a chance to talk with Ainoma-chan, and she said she would like to talk with both of us,
So I invited them to Bolty Bee,
We'll go to a food stall together, right? What do you call it?
A calligraphy garden, and all kinds of things.
We used to do that at summer festivals.
We had a wion and other things,
Nana-chan put her shoulder on Mr. Setoguchi's shoulder in the shoniwa,
She fell asleep in the garden,
But you know, since then, she has talked to me a lot,
She told me she wanted to come back again,
I think she must have been able to get through to my heart and shoulders,
I think I was able to win his heart and his shoulder.
At that time, I wanted a big Umaibo,
Normally, I would have asked the guest to hold a good stick,
I would have asked a guest to hold a good stick or something, but Mr. Setoguchi was holding a good stick for me,
I would have asked him to hold the stick and support me,
And on top of that, I hit him.
I hit Setoguchi-san who was supporting me.
His reaction was 120%.
That was amazing.
But afterwards, I told him I was sorry, and he said it was totally fine.
There was some kind of mission card on the back of the car-like product,
There was a mission card on the back of the car-like products, and Nana-chan took a good stick from it,
I thought it was something I wanted to apologize for now,
Yes, that's right.
But I always get stuck on the theme,
I've had such an incident,
I want to be saved.
I didn't know you had a case like that.
It's said that God is in control, isn't it?
It was a nice flow.
It was really interesting.
Wasn't there a "Milky, Milky" at that time?
Yes, I think so.
I wonder if they did, Milky.
I wonder if it was.
At that time, it was that, wasn't it?
We didn't scoop goldfish by ourselves,
We drew a picture of our house.
We did that too.
I don't think we had much milky.
But we ate it.
We endured it.
I see.
That was fun.
It was fun.
After that, it was just the two of us in adult time,
Eechi stayed behind,
Talking and stuff, right?
Yes, that's right.
So please come back and watch it again.
Yes, I will. Thank you very much.
This is the last person.
That's me.
Can I give you a little more reaction?
Milky, please.
She wants more response.
Don't notice.
And finally, here she is.
Nenaha!
Thank you very much.
I don't know what to say to a little girl.
Excuse me.
I'll go.
My subject.
You could tell I didn't cook that kid much.
This is that very popular corner,
I was thinking about this when we played the very popular "We're all in this together" game,
In this game, we were given a theme,
If everyone had the same theme, it was the correct answer,
But at that time, the theme was "What do you think of this thing?
That's right.
I wondered what everyone would think of when I played with them,
I think I think in that direction,
But I was thinking in the direction of "What is this thing?
I thought, "That's enough,
But when I answered "pork cutlet," my answer was totally wrong.
It wasn't this thing at first.
At that time.
Yes, it was. At that time.
But now, I think that Bolt's "pork cutlet" is called "tonkatsu".
I think,
That's right.
I really felt at that time that I should have been cooking.
Then I started to do a little bit more.
Just a little bit!
That brings back memories.
I miss it.I missed it.
But it might have had the biggest impact.
All teen.
Something like, in order, Kodamono, Seino, and John,
Oh, not John.
John.
What's that?
He said takoyaki, takoyaki, and Nano-chan was in tears,
Tonkatsu?
No, it's not takoyaki. There it was.
Did you have it?
Let's hide it.
Say, "Hang on.
You looked really worried.
I was so killjoy,
I was sorry on the way home.
He said he was done with pork cutlets,
I said, "No, Nano-chan was really funny,
I'm sorry, Tonkatsu is not this man.
It was over.
It was embarrassing.
By the way, what do you think tonkatsu is?
What is it?
It's just a little image.
But that's how it is in everyone's mind.
You're all so sweet.
Just for this one time.
I don't know, we've run out of ideas.
There's been a lot going on.
Especially the time of the Corona disaster.
Runchie and I...
We did it remotely while delivering the message.
Then, you were the target.
And Ayanoro-chan was on the same screen.
We all did it remotely.
That was fun.
Ayanoro-chan comes up with some kind of riddle.
What's its name?
What was it?
It was there, wasn't it?
Yes, there were.
I don't remember any of them.
I don't know.
He wasn't that cute.
He thought about it.
I was looking back at the videos from back then.
And then I was like, "I'd like to put it out now.
Like...
I was like this.
It was a little embarrassing.
Also, I saw that you practiced for the online signing. Yesterday.
Oh, yes.
Yes yes yes.
That's about the third one, right?
Yes, that's right.
I was really, really surprised at the two of them,
I said, "Let's practice the online signing session,
We are doing a lot of online signing sessions now,
So I said, "Let's do an online autograph session,
It was kind of funny,
It was a bit funny.
I bet you must have been in trouble at the time.
Daikon-chan.
It was like, "As long as I'm over these two, I'll be fine.
I remember how embarrassing it was.
I was so embarrassed.
I miss those days.
I don't know....
So, I'm sure you all have various memorable scenes,
I'd like to ask you about them, but I don't have time.
I won't listen to them.
Please write about various things.
Please write in the comments section.
Yes, I will.
Now, so I've announced the 00 Ambassadors,
We had a lot of games and quizzes on Vol TV,
I think this was probably the most interesting one among them,
Yay, you are here today.
Wow.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
You're not fishing?
No fishing?
Not fishing?
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Please, title call.
Okay, okay. Here we go.
Let's go!
Tell them how you feel with a niburi teburi!
Jechal Quiz Contest
The Last
The End
Thank you very much!
We have developed to the point of doing it together with everyone in the Lily Club, but this is the first time for us.
This is the first time for us to have a scoring meeting.
The first time, the first and second time, Ayana had a terrible expression on her face.
She had a terrible expression on her face.
Ayaan, you're funny.
Please fix it when it's really funny.
Aya-chan is going to give you a question.
She's already got a great expression on her face.
She doesn't even react when she gets it right.
She's cute.
She's adorable.
You're really growing up.
I'll do it again today... with no expression on my face.
Don't do that.
I'll do it with a smile.
And have fun.
So, we've done a lot of work on the team.
I'd like you to fight with Lunch and Ayana.
Thank you very much.
As I'm sure you all know.
Each team will decide who will do the gesture and who will answer.
You have to decide who will do the gesture and who will answer.
The team with the most correct answers in one minute wins.
We have a prize for you today.
Hey, powder... not powder...
Here it is.
Rice flour.
Oatmeal cookies and
Salted chocolate chip cookies.
One of these big ones.
I had them put on it, so...
I hope you have a great time.
Please decide on a candidate for the second round.
Okay.
Then, Aya, please choose from among the rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
Yes, Aya-chan.
Yes, ma'am.
Light rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors
rock, paper, scissors rock, paper, scissors
Ball and rock-paper-scissors rock-paper-scissors poi
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors
LOL!
Then I'll go ahead.
I'll go ahead.
Applause
Applause.
Congratulations.
Those of you who are going to play the gesture game, please go down one step to the right side,
If you can't see, you can stand up.
Oh, no. I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
That's funny.Interesting.
Which one of you guys does the gesture?
Whoo.
Can you see it?
I see it.
Thank you very much.
This way?
Is this, uh, one-minute time okay?
Um, it's going to be sound.
Which way is the SE for that time?
It's coming from this side. Oh, hi.
Okay, let's go.
When I get to 30 seconds, I'll say 30 seconds ago,
Okay.
Oh.
Okay, um..,
Why are you smiling?
I'm scared.
Here we go.
With the face I'm gesturing with,
I'm still going to answer.
Yes.
Here you go.
Here we go.
Okay, yes.
Elevator.
Correct.
Uh, morning exercises.
Uh, no.
Preparation exercises are different. Gymnastics are different.
You know what I'm talking about.
Morning exercises
Let's see... Nunatsu...
Oh, wait a minute.
Sadly, I'll pass.
That's right.
Nanuke, it's not morning exercises.
I'll pass. I'll pass.
I'll pass.
Yes, kiss me.
I'll know if you touch me backwards for a second.
Eh, spaceman spaceman
Oh, it's over.
It's not over.
Zombie.
Cherry blossoms, cherry blossoms, weeping cherry blossoms...
Yes, it's over.
I'm sorry, I'm only 4 seconds over.
Yes, sir.
Wait, I couldn't figure out the sad one.
I'm sorry.
Did you get the first three correct?
Three.
Oh, not so many... 3 questions.
Not many.
But I want you to guess that one.
Just that one.
I told you before.
Not the, uh, not the head ricer.
Not, uh, not the ABCs or anything.
That's right.
That one start.
A4 first place
First place in A4
Genre Icon
Applause
Bye-bye!
I am your fan! please do not hesitate to contact me
Conditions.
Radio. Radio.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Which one is it? Aya?
Does it work?
It's working. Yes, it's working.
Yes, please.
I'll do my best.
Would you like the answer on the left, please?
Yes, I'll do my best.
I'll do my best.
Here we go.
Okay, let's start!
Onigiri
Jetcaster
Walk
Escalator.
Which one?
Aya!
I lost 30 seconds.
Aya, the gesture game.
Oh! I like that one.
Yeah, one.
Magic!
Correct!
What?
Do you want to cut it?
Yes, it's done!
Let's try that last one again.
What?
You know, I'm sure you'll figure it out.
You know what I mean?
I'm sure you'll get it.
KENKENPA!
Ah!
Okay, I'm gonna go fast.
Okay.
What's that? What's on your leg?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
ah-ha-ha-ha
A-ha-ha-ha
Huh?
Ha-ha-ha-ha
Applause
That's good.
Congratulations.
Applause.
You're not done yet.
How many did you get right?
Two.
What's that?
Oh, my God, it's true.
Lunchie's team wins.
Congratulations, sir.
Please come back.
No way.
It's always for games and quizzes and stuff.
Everyone is like, "Isn't Ayana's team going to win? Like that.
There were a lot of them.
Then these cookies...
I'll give them to everyone.
You can take pictures.
Photographs.
Can I have one? Here.
Thank you very much.
I had a good time.
That's fine.
Yes, thank you.
And that's it for the gesture quiz competition.
I feel like I could watch this forever.
It's really time to go.
It's early, isn't it?
So fast.
Really.I really do.
I could go on forever.
Please, come in.
Oh, I'm here alone.
No one is answering.
It's fun. It's fun.
So, unfortunately, it's time for me to go,
So, do you have a few announcements and things like that?
Yes, I do. The final episode of this Volt TV special, which is being recorded in public right now
It will be uploaded to the official Bolt YouTube channel later today.
I would be happy if you all could watch the streaming as well.
I'm looking forward to hearing your comments.
We're looking forward to hearing from you.
And I have one question for you all.
Oh?
What day is April 11?
Aya's birthday!
That's great!
Ta-da!
BIG HORN!
The date is April 11, and we will be doing Stacomi, Soul Room, and InstaLive from 6pm.
Today is the day of the event, and I'll be able to deliver it on the same day.
I'll be playing some fun games and stuff.
Please come and watch!
I'm only 14.
I know.
Seino
Happy Birthday to you!
Happy Birthday to you
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to you.
[Applause]
Thank you very much.
Let's see.
I thought there was nothing going on today, but...
I'm so surprised.
Thank you very much.
And it's my favorite, Strawberry!
I am only 14 years old, but I will try my best to make my 15th year a year when I can bring smiles to everyone's faces.
Thank you very much, everyone.
So, will we have this cake together this time?
Oh, yes. Of course, everyone.
Shall we eat it?
Yes, we will eat it.
I'll eat it.
Well then, let's take a commemorative photo in front of everyone, shall we?
Yes. I'm so happy.
Let's go.
Ta-da!
Oh, so that's how it is.
Yeah, that's how it is.
Let's go!
Well, let's all say...
Happy Birthday Aya!
Let's say "Happy Birthday Aya-chan!
Let's go!
Happy Birthday Aya-chan!
Wow!
Oh!
Ooh.
Ooh-oh.
[Applause]
Come on, let's keep the cake.
What are you gonna buy?
You're gonna have a lot of food later.
You're gonna eat it?
Please don't eat it.
Let's eat.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Congratulations.
And maybe I should have at least done a self book instead.
Okay, I'll give you that on the day of delivery.
Yes, bye. So that's the last one.
Let's have a word or two for all of you who have been watching Voltiview and for all of you who have been so supportive.
Yes, please.
Please do.
Okay, I will start.
Well, thank you all very much for coming to the open Voltibee and watching the broadcast today.
I was just thinking about what I was going to talk about and how I was going to talk about a lot of my memories of BolTV.
I'm so happy that you celebrated my birthday.
My heart is really full of gratitude!
Thank you all so much!
I turned 15 years old...
I'm also turning 15 years old... oh, I'm turning 15 years old...
Anyway, I've been doing Vol TV since I was in the fifth grade.
I've been doing it right after it started with Bol.
I didn't have a chance to talk much.
I didn't have a chance to talk much, but I was given a chance to talk on Vol TV.
I might have had a blank expression like that in the beginning.
But we had a good time talking.
Thanks to Vol TV
I was able to make friends with everyone at first.
I really think that Vol TV will be my treasured video.
And today is also a treasure.
I played a lot of games.
We played a lot of games, and you all participated in the public Volt TV and other events.
I had a lot of fun with everyone who joined in with me.
I really had a great time with you all.
Thank you all so much!
Yes, to all of you who came today, and to all of you who will be watching the broadcast in a few hours,
And to those of you who have been watching Vol. TV, thank you so much.
Yes, I really appreciate it. As both Aya and Amanokori said,
In the beginning, I might have been like a quiet girl, without any expression.
But now I am like this and everyone has brought out a lot of laughter from me,
Thank you very much.
In the past, I often wondered why I couldn't go home or do things like that, and there were many times when I felt sorry for myself,
Now I have things to reflect on, but I was really happy to have the opportunity to express myself in this way,
I was also happy to have this opportunity to show myself as I am now, even when it was difficult to meet everyone in person at the Corona Disaster,
I was also very happy to be able to see everyone through the screen when I was unable to meet them in person due to the Corona disaster.
I have a lot of memories of Vol. TV and I will be watching a lot more,
I will be watching a lot of Vol. TV from now on, so please watch the archives as much as you can.
Thank you very much.
Yes, thank you so much to all of you who have come today and to those of you who are watching via the streaming service.
At first, we didn't know what to talk about or what games to play.
We were not sure what to talk about or what games to play, and then the voice of heaven appeared as a character.
And then, when I was at work, or when I came back home, you all commented and watched the show.
Thanks to all of you who commented and watched the games.
I've been able to play so many games
I am so thankful for all the games and open recordings
I'm really filled with gratitude.
I also appreciate the videos where we all laughed so much.
I can still laugh when I watch them the next day.
I also think that videos like this, where we all laughed so much
I always think that it will be a video that I can look back on in years to come.
I hope you all will, too, when something happens.
I would be happy if you could look back at your favorite times.
Thank you very much.
[Applause] Yes, thank you so much for coming today.
Yes, thank you all so much for coming today.
And thank you all for watching on the distribution.
It's the last three rounds, and it's the last time I've been able to hear you all laugh live in front of everyone,
I was really happy to be able to hear everyone's laughter live in front of everyone and to be able to perform with Koike-san, who was on hand, and we had a lot of fun and laughter right up to the end.
As the godparents of the name "Bol TV," what can I say?
As a godparent, I don't really have anything special to say,
But I have been broadcasting live on YouTube since before I decided on the name Bol TV,
Some people came to know about our atmosphere through watching Volt TV, and some people came to like Volt from there,
I was really happy to see that, and I felt that Team Bolt was overflowing with love,
I think that Volt TV was the most wonderful program that conveyed the love of Team Bolt even through the screen,
I think it was a wonderful program that conveyed the love of Team Bolt in every episode, even through the screen, and that's before I say it to myself,
I also look back on it and feel a little embarrassed,
There were times when I was a little embarrassed, such as at the graduation ceremony when I didn't know my mother was there, or when I cried,
I hope you all enjoy the show, including these episodes, and I hope you will come and watch it again on Volt TV.If you find any interesting moments on Bol TV, please look back and see if you can find any more,
I hope you will also look back and enjoy the past Volt TV episodes as well,
I hope that the past episodes of Vol TV will also be a fun time for everyone.
Thank you very much for your time. This is Vol TV.
Shall we close this session?
Yes, let's close this session. Thank you very much for your time today.
Thank you very much.
Yes, there will be more after this, including the final scoring session,
I hope you will enjoy it as well.
And, you know, there is only one week left until the last live performance,
I will do my best until the end,
I will do my best until the end, so please give me your support until the end.
Thank you very much for your support.
That's all for now, that's all for us, Bolt.
Thank you very much.
Bye bye.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
Try licking this, you'll see what everyone knows best.
Thank you. - Bye-bye.
Bye-bye.
I am
Abracadabra
Bye-bye.
bye-bye!
traces of family
weiterhin
Bye-bye.
Let's have a final round of applause.
Thank you.
Bye-bye.
ș
So, the Morning Musume.' 15 final session is over.
Thank you very much.
It was fun, wasn't it?
It was a lot of fun.
Thank you very much for watching the live recording of the last episode.
Thank you very much.
It was over in a second.
It was over in seconds.
It was the first one,
I was more and more excited than ever before,
I'll tell you what I said.
And today, I was allowed to be a little more vocal,
I was so happy that all the fans got so excited.
I also didn't expect to have my birthday celebrated here,
So I was very happy. Thank you very much.
Let's eat cake together.
I knew it was the best cake when I was 15 years old.
I just realized.
If the day comes when I come back again at the end of this,
See you.
Great.
See you later.
Thank you very much.
I really look back,
As I look back today, I have so many happy memories,
I'm sure there are times that you haven't seen them yet,
I'm sure there are times that you haven't seen yet, so I hope you will continue to enjoy those times as well.
Thank you very much for watching VOL.
Thank you very much.
So, that's us, VOL.
Bye bye.
Se-no.
Ah, ah, ah, se-no
Meow.